[
    {
        "question": "Who invented Javascript?",
        "choice1": "Brendan Eich",
        "choice2": "Brendan Schider",
        "choice3":"Brendan Ferguson",
        "choice4":"Brendan Turgenev",
        "answer":1
    },
    {
        "question": "How can you get the total number of arguments passed to a function?",
        "choice1": "Using args.length property",
        "choice2":"Using arguments.length property",
        "choice3": "Both of the above.",
        "choice4":"None of the above.",
        "answer":2
    },
    {
        "question":"Which built-in method calls a function for each element in the array?",
        "choice1":"while()",
        "choice2":"loop()",
        "choice3":"forEach()",
        "choice4":"None of the above.",
        "answer":3
    
    },
    {
        "question":"Which built-in method returns the calling string value converted to upper case?",
        "choice1":"toUpperCase()",
        "choice2":"toUpper()",
        "choice3":"changeCase(case)",
        "choice4":"None of the above.",
        "answer":1
    },
    {
        "question":"Which of the following function of Boolean object returns a string of either 'true' or 'false' depending upon the value of the object?",
        "choice1":"toSource()",
        "choice2":"valueOf()",
        "choice3":"toString()",
        "choice4":"None of the above.",
        "answer":3
    },
    {
        "question":"Which of the following function of String object returns the characters in a string beginning at the specified location through the specified number of characters?",
        "choice1":"slice()",
        "choice2":"split()",
        "choice3":"substr()",
        "choice4":"search()",
        "answer":3
    },
    {
        "question":"Which of the following function of String object creates an HTML anchor that is used as a hypertext target?",
        "choice1":"anchor()",
        "choice2":"link()",
        "choice3":"blink()",
        "choice4":"big()",
        "answer":1
    },
    {
        "question":"Which of the following function of String object causes a string to be italic, as if it were in an <i> tag?",
        "choice1":"fixed()",
        "choice2":"fontcolor()",
        "choice3":"fontsize(",
        "choice4":"italics()",
        "ans0wer":4
    },
    {
        "question":"Which of the following function of Array object joins all elements of an array into a string?",
        "choice1":"concat()",
        "choice2":"join()",
        "choice3":"pop()",
        "choice4":"map()",
        "answer":2
    },
    {
        "question":"Which of the following function of Array object returns a string representing the array and its elements?",
        "choice1":"toSource()",
        "choice2":"sort()",
        "choice3":"splice()",
        "choice4":"toString()",
        "answer":4
    }
  ]